CHARLES LAMB

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Diligent software engineer excelling in highly collaborative work environments, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and Mongo DB. Responding to challenges with a detailed UX implementation skillset as well as developing time complexity based solutions.

WORK HISTORY

Quality Assurance Analyst, 03/2019 to 11/2019 EIA Electric, New York, United States

 Identified and tracked defects with software and supported developers in resolving problems by completing additional tests

Real Estate Agent, 03/2016 to 03/2019 Keller Williams, New York, United States

- Represented buyers and sellers of developed and undeveloped properties
- Advised prospective clients on current market activities

Samsung Experience Manager, 05/2014 to 02/2016 Mosaic Sales Solutions, New York, United States

 Increased customer satisfaction and repeat business through relentless pursuit of resolutions to problems arising from Samsung Experience footprint, protecting company reputation and loyal client base

Google Technology Lead, 07/2012 to 03/2014 Marketstar, New York, United States

- Managed quality assurance program including on site evaluations, internal audits and customer surveys
- Worked with Retail clients to understand requirements and provide exceptional field marketing service

Address: New York, NY 11435

Phone: (929) 307-6880

Email: Charles.lamb.dev@gmail.com

Website: www.charleslambjr.com

Github: www.github.com/cyberstizz

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in

/charles-lamb-jr/

SKILLS

- Javascript, React, Node, Express
- Java, Ruby, Rails
- Python, Django
- MongoDB, MySQL
- REST, OAuth, JSON
- Css, Bootstrap, Sass, Html

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Bootcamp, Full Stack Development, Expected in 05/2020

Per Scholas - New York, NY

Audio Engineer, Engineering Acoustics, 2005 Institute of Audio Research - New York, NY